<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="connected_via_wfa">Connected via WLAN assistant</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_off">WLAN off.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_no_wifi">WLAN disconnected.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_one_bar">WLAN one bar.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_two_bars">WLAN two bars.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_three_bars">WLAN three bars.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_signal_full">WLAN signal full.</string>
    <string name="wifi_verbose_logging">Enable WLAN verbose logging</string>
    <string name="wifi_aggressive_handover">Aggressive WLAN to cellular handover</string>
    <string name="wifi_allow_scan_with_traffic">Always allow WLAN roaming scans</string>
    <string name="wifi_verbose_logging_summary">Increase WLAN logging level and show per SSID RSSI in WLAN picker</string>
    <string name="wifi_aggressive_handover_summary">When enabled, WLAN will be more aggressive in handing over the data connection to cellular when the WLAN signal is low</string>
    <string name="wifi_allow_scan_with_traffic_summary">Allow/Restrict WLAN roaming scans based on the amount of data traffic present at the interface</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_always_on_summary">Always keep mobile data active, even when WLAN is active (for fast network switching)</string>
    <string name="radio_controls_summary">Manage WLAN, Bluetooth, airplane mode, mobile networks, &amp; VPNs</string>
    <string name="wifi_assistant_title">WLAN Assistant</string>
    <string name="wifi_quick_toggle_title">WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_quick_toggle_summary">Turn on WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings">WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings_category">WLAN settings</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings_title">WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_wizard_title">Select WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_select_network">Select WLAN network</string>
    <string name="wifi_starting">Turning WLAN on…</string>
    <string name="wifi_stopping">Turning off WLAN…</string>
    <string name="wifi_poor_network_detection_summary">Avoid connecting to WLAN networks with poor connectivity</string>
    <string name="wifi_automatically_connect_title">Auto-use open WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_automatically_connect_summary">Let WLAN assistant auto-connect to open networks with good Internet connections</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_notify_text">To improve location accuracy, system apps and services can still scan for WLAN networks. You can change this in LINK_BEGINscanning settingsLINK_END.</string>
    <string name="wifi_setting_sleep_policy_title">Keep WLAN on during sleep</string>
    <string name="wifi_suspend_optimizations">WLAN optimization</string>
    <string name="wifi_suspend_optimizations_summary">Minimize battery usage when WLAN is on</string>
    <string name="wifi_access_points">WLAN networks</string>
    <string name="wifi_menu_p2p">WLAN Direct</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_wifi_off">To see available networks, turn WLAN on.</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_wifi_on">Searching for WLAN networks…</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_user_restricted">"You don't have permission to change the WLAN network."</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_setup_title">WLAN Protected Setup</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_onstart_pbc">Press the WLAN Protected Setup button on your router. It may be called \"WPS\" or contain this symbol:</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_onstart_pin">Enter pin %1$s on your WLAN router. The setup can take up to two minutes to complete.</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_connected">Connected to WLAN network %s</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_always_turnon_message">"To improve location accuracy and for other purposes, %1$s wants to turn on network scanning, even when WLAN is off.

Allow this for all apps that want to scan?"</string>
    <string name="wifi_skipped_message">"WARNING: You may incur extra carrier data fees.

Phone setup may require significant network activity."</string>
    <string name="wifi_and_mobile_skipped_message">"WARNING: The phone won't be able to verify that your software is up to date."</string>
    <string name="wifi_connect_failed_message">The phone was unable to connect to this WLAN network.</string>
    <string name="wifi_advanced_titlebar">Advanced WLAN settings</string>
    <string name="wifi_configure_titlebar">Configure WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_advanced_not_available">WLAN advanced settings are not available for this user</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_settings_title">WLAN Direct</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_checkbox_text">Portable WLAN hotspot</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_failed_subtext">Portable WLAN hotspot error</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_ap_text">Configure WLAN hotspot</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_subtext">%1$s %2$s portable WLAN hotspot</string>
    <string name="testing_wifi_info">WLAN information</string>
    <string name="wifi_api_test">WLAN API</string>
    <string name="wifi_status_test">WLAN status</string>
    <string name="wifi_state_label">WLAN state:</string>
    <string name="wifi_config_info">WLAN config</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_settings_title">WLAN calling settings</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_suggestion_title">Enable WLAN calling</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_suggestion_summary">Use WLAN instead of mobile network</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_mode_title">WLAN calling</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_mode_dialog_title">WLAN calling mode</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_off_explanation">When WLAN calling is on, your phone can route calls via WLAN networks or your carrier’s network, depending on your preference and which signal is stronger. Before turning on this feature, check with your carrier regarding fees and other details.</string>
    <string name="status_wifi_mac_address">WLAN MAC address</string>
    <string name="reset_network_desc">"This will reset all network settings, including:

"<li>WLAN</li>"
"<li>Mobile data</li>"
"<li>Bluetooth</li></string>
    <string name="network_scorer_change_active_dialog_title">Change WLAN assistant?</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_description">Use GPS, WLAN and mobile networks to estimate location</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_description">Use WLAN and mobile networks to estimate location</string>
    <string name="location_scanning_wifi_always_scanning_title">WLAN scanning</string>
    <string name="location_scanning_wifi_always_scanning_description">Improve location by allowing system apps and services to detect WLAN networks at any time</string>
    <string name="location_network_based">WLAN &amp; mobile network location</string>
    <string name="location_neighborhood_level">Let apps use data from sources such as WLAN and mobile networks to determine your approximate location</string>
    <string name="location_neighborhood_level_wifi">Location determined by WLAN</string>
    <string name="battery_stats_wifi_running_label">WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_on_time">WLAN on time</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_on_time">WLAN on time</string>
    <string name="power_wifi">WLAN</string>
    <string name="usage_type_wifi_running">WLAN running</string>
    <string name="usage_type_data_wifi_send">WLAN data sent</string>
    <string name="usage_type_data_wifi_recv">WLAN data received</string>
    <string name="battery_action_wifi">WLAN settings</string>
    <string name="battery_desc_wifi">Battery used by WLAN</string>
    <string name="battery_sugg_wifi">"Turn off WLAN when not using it or when it isn't available"</string>
    <string name="gadget_toggle_wifi">Updating WLAN setting</string>
    <string name="gadget_state_template">%1$s %2$s</string>
    <string name="gadget_wifi">WLAN</string>
    <string name="backup_data_summary">Back up app data, WLAN passwords, and other settings to Google servers</string>
    <string name="backup_erase_dialog_message">Stop backing up your WLAN passwords, bookmarks, other settings, and app data, plus erase all copies on Google servers?</string>
    <string name="fullbackup_erase_dialog_message">Stop backing up device data (such as WLAN passwords and call history) and app data (such as settings and files stored by apps), and erase all copies on Google Drive?</string>
    <string name="fullbackup_data_summary">"Automatically back up device data (such as WLAN passwords and call history) and app data (such as settings and files stored by apps) remotely.

When you turn on automatic backup, device and app data is periodically saved remotely. App data can be any data that an app has saved (based on developer settings), including potentially sensitive data such as contacts, messages, and photos."</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title">WLAN setup</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_editing_network">Connect to WLAN network %s</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_connecting_network">Connecting to WLAN network %s…</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_eap_not_supported">"You can't configure an EAP WLAN connection during setup. After setup, you can do that in Settings > Wireless &amp; networks."</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_description_connected">Touch <b>Next</b>" to continue with setup.

Touch "<b>Back</b> to connect to a different WLAN network.</string>
    <string name="data_usage_menu_show_wifi">Show WLAN usage</string>
    <string name="data_usage_menu_hide_wifi">Hide WLAN</string>
    <string name="data_usage_disable_wifi_limit">Set WLAN data limit</string>
    <string name="data_usage_tab_wifi">WLAN</string>
    <string name="data_usage_app_restrict_background_summary">Disable background data on mobile data network only. WLAN will be used if available.</string>
    <string name="data_usage_app_restrict_dialog">"This feature may cause an app that depends on background data to stop working when WLAN isn't available.

Check settings within the app to see if there are more appropriate data usage controls available."</string>
    <string name="data_usage_restrict_background">"If you restrict background mobile data, some apps and services won't work unless you're connected to a WLAN network."</string>
    <string name="data_usage_restrict_background_multiuser">"If you restrict background mobile data, some apps and services won't work unless you're connected to a WLAN network.

This setting affects all users on this phone."</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_body">Select the WLAN networks that are mobile hotspots. Apps can be restricted from using these networks when running in the background. Apps may also generate warnings when using these networks for large downloads.</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_wifi">WLAN networks</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_wifi_disabled">To select mobile hotspots, turn WLAN on.</string>
    <string name="user_add_user_message_long">"You can share this device with other people by creating additional users. Each user has their own space, which they can customize with their own apps, wallpaper, and so on. Users can also adjust tablet settings like WLAN that affect everyone.

After you create a new user, that person needs to go through a setup process.

Any user can accept updated app permissions on behalf of all other users."</string>
    <string name="restriction_wifi_config_title">WLAN and mobile data</string>
    <string name="restriction_wifi_config_summary">Allow modification of WLAN and mobile network settings</string>
    <string name="keywords_wifi">WLAN network connection</string>
    <string name="keywords_wifi_calling">WLAN WLAN call calling</string>
    <string name="setup_wifi_nfc_tag">Set up WLAN NFC tag</string>
    <string name="condition_hotspot_summary">Portable WLAN hotspot %1$s is active. WLAN for this device has been turned off.</string>
    <string name="condition_airplane_summary">"WLAN, Bluetooth, and mobile data network are turned off. You can't make phone calls or connect to the Internet."</string>
    <string name="condition_cellular_summary">Internet is available only via WLAN</string>
    <string name="condition_bg_data_summary">Background data is only available via WLAN. This may affect some apps or services when WLAN is not available.</string>
    <string name="wifi">WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_bridge_checkbox_text">WLAN bridge</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_bridge_tittle_text">WLAN bridge settings</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_bridge_text">Configure WLAN bridge</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_settings_summary">Set the bridge name, password, and more</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_details">"1. WLAN bridge can significantly improve the transmission range and intensity of WLAN signals. Other devices can be connected to your current WLAN network through your device.
2. WLAN bridge supports access from up to 4 devices.
3. WLAN bridge does not work with the WLAN hotspot and WLAN Direct features. If WLAN bridge is enabled, some applications that use P2P services may not work properly.
4. Using WLAN bridge consumes your battery power faster."</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_switch_nowifi_summary">WLAN connection required</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_switch_wifi_summary">Share connected WLAN network</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_connected_network_Toast">Connected to WLAN network %s</string>
    <string name="huawei_beam_explained">Huawei Beam lets you transfer files, such as pictures, videos, contacts and URLs, between your device and another NFC-capable device. Huawei Beam is activated by placing the two devices close together (usually back to back) and tapping your screen. Please note that your Bluetooth or WLAN may be turned on automatically before file transmission.</string>
    <string name="wifi_display_settings_summary">Display your phone screen on another display over a WLAN connection</string>
    <string name="cell_switch_to_wifi_prompt">WLAN networks %s available. Do you want to stop data service and connect to a WLAN network?</string>
    <string name="switch_to_wifi_manual_prompt">Found WLAN signal, would you like to use this WLAN network?</string>
    <string name="switch_to_wifi_query_prompt">WLAN networks %s available. Do you want to connect to a WLAN network?</string>
    <string name="wifi_to_wifi_prompt">Current connection signal is weak, would you like to use another WLAN network?</string>
    <string name="advanced_wifi_settings_title">Advanced settings</string>
    <string name="huawei_beam_front_explained">"Huawei Beam lets you transfer files to other NFC devices by placing the devices close together. For example, you can wirelessly transfer pictures, videos, contacts, URLs, and more between two NFC-capable devices. Simply:
1. Place the front panel of your device against another NFC device, and pick up your device after you hear a tone.
2. Touch your screen within three seconds of hearing the tone.
3. Place the front panel of your device against the other NFC device again to complete the transfer. Please note that your Bluetooth or WLAN may be turned on automatically before file transmission."</string>
    <string name="wifiap_use_help_details">"1. You can use a portable WLAN hotspot device as your Internet access point. Peripherals can be connected to your device through the WLAN and connected devices will access the Internet through the mobile network.
2. Using a portable WLAN hotspot will require your mobile data connection to be on, and will consume some data traffic.
3. Using a portable WLAN hotspot may drain your battery life faster."</string>
    <string name="wifiap_connect_help_details_open">"Manual connection:
1. Turn on WLAN on the target device, and find the hotspot %1$s.
2. Connect to the hotspot."</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_title">China Mobile WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_warning">You are connected to a China Mobile WLAN network. Using this network may produce applicable WLAN usage fees.</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_never_notify">Do not remind again</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_notify_switch">China Mobile WLAN reminder</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_notify_summary">"Remind me when I'm connected to a China Mobile WLAN network"</string>
    <string name="wifi_cmcc_no_notification_summary">Do not display any notifications when switching networks (mobile data to WLAN and vice versa, or between WLAN networks)</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_description_wifionly">Use GPS and WLAN to estimate location</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_description_wifionly">Use WLAN to estimate location</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_title">WLAN+</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_summary">Intelligently select WLAN or mobile data network</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description">"When WLAN+ is enabled, your WLAN connectivity will be evaluated to provide smart network switching (WLAN data usage may increase). WLAN+ automatically:
1. Switches between WLAN and mobile data (with notifications) to provide a smooth Internet experience.
2. Turns on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it."</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_settings_title">WLAN+ settings</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_intelligent_switch_description">Intelligently switch between WLAN and mobile data networks for a better Internet experience.</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_auto_turn_on_description">Automatically turn on WLAN when you approach a known location.</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_global_description">"When WLAN+ is enabled, your WLAN connectivity will be evaluated to provide smart network switching (WLAN data usage may increase). WLAN+ automatically:
1. Switches between WLAN and mobile data to provide a smooth Internet experience.
2. Turns on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it."</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_title_emui">Use GPS, WLAN, and mobile networks</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_title_emui">Use WLAN and mobile networks</string>
    <string name="pgps_switch_title">GPS acceleration</string>
    <string name="pgps_switch_summary">Allow GPS to collect nearby cellular base station and WLAN data to provide quicker and more accurate location services</string>
    <string name="find_no_wlan_ap">Unable to find WLAN hotspot</string>
    <string name="cannot_connect_wlan">Unable to connect to WLAN</string>
    <string name="cannot_login_internet_with_wlan">Unable to access Internet over WLAN</string>
    <string name="wfd_connect_fail">WLAN Direct connection failed</string>
    <string name="find_no_wfd_device">Unable to find WLAN Direct device</string>
    <string name="wfd_search_no_devices_causes">"No available devices found, it may be that:
1. The paired device is not discoverable.
2. The paired device is experiencing technical issues. Try restarting WLAN and re-open WLAN Direct.
3. Your own device is experiencing technical issues. Try restarting WLAN and re-open WLAN Direct."</string>
    <string name="wfd_connected_failed_causes">"The connection could not be established. Possible reasons:
1. The paired device didn't accept the connection request.
2. Either device has already established another WLAN Direct connection.
3. The paired device is experiencing technical issues. Try restarting it."</string>
    <string name="wifi_qrcode_share_notice">Scan the QR code to connect to this WLAN network</string>
    <string name="devices_not_found_solution_title">"If the device can't be found, try the following:"</string>
    <string name="devices_not_found_solution_message">"1. Make sure the device is scanning for other devices.
2. If the peer device is experiencing issues, restart WLAN and access WLAN Direct again.
3. If your device is experiencing issues, restart WLAN and access WLAN Direct again."</string>
    <string name="devices_not_connected_solution_message">"1. Make sure that the peer device has accepted the connection request.
2. Make sure both devices have not connected to other devices.
3. If the peer device is experiencing issues, try reconnecting."</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description_emui">"When WLAN+ is enabled, your WLAN connectivity will be evaluated to provide smart network switching (WLAN data usage may increase). WLAN+ automatically:
1. Switches between WLAN and mobile data (You can select the default switching mode in the mobile network settings) to provide a smooth Internet experience.
2. Turns on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it."</string>
    <string name="link_plus_live_update_description">When Link+ live update is enabled, your phone automatically updates the data of communication parameters through your wireless network (WLAN by default) in order to improve relevant Link+ features.</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description_emui2">"When WLAN+ is enabled, your WLAN connectivity will be evaluated to provide smart network switching (WLAN data usage may increase). WLAN+ automatically:
1. Switches between WLAN and mobile data (You can select the default switching mode in the mobile network settings) to provide a smooth Internet experience.
2. Turns on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it.
3. Evaluates available WLAN networks. Device will not auto-connect to saved networks without an Internet connection.
4. For some free WLAN hotspots, obtains the verification code from the incoming SMS message and logs into the network via the browser (currently only supported in China)."</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_global_description2">"When WLAN+ is enabled, your WLAN connectivity will be evaluated to provide smart network switching (WLAN data usage may increase). WLAN+ automatically:
1. Switches between WLAN and mobile data to provide a smooth Internet experience.
2. Turns on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it.
3. Evaluates available WLAN networks. Device will not auto-connect to saved networks without an Internet connection."</string>
    <string name="help_message">"1. Your printer and phone aren't connected to the same WLAN network.
2. Your printer doesn't support this particular printing service (confirm with manufacturer).
3. Searching has timed out. Try again if this is the case.
4. Your printer has crashed. Restart your printer and try again."</string>
    <string name="wifi_cloud_security_check_title">WLAN security check</string>
    <string name="wifi_cloud_security_check_summary">Check the security level of connected WLAN networks through Phone Manager, and pause auto-connect to saved networks that pose security risks</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description_emui3">"When WLAN+ is enabled, your WLAN connectivity will be evaluated to provide smart network switching, and it will automatically update the optimization parameters through WLAN (WLAN data usage may increase). WLAN+ automatically:
1. Switches between WLAN and mobile data (You can select the default switching mode in the mobile network settings) to provide a smooth Internet experience.
2. Turns on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it.
3. Evaluates available WLAN networks. For saved networks that have no Internet access, auto-connect is paused.
4. For certain free WLAN hotspots, detects and accesses the verification code from the incoming SMS verification message and logs into the network via the browser automatically (currently only supported in China)."</string>
    <string name="user_add_user_message">"You can share this device with other people by creating additional users. Each user has their own space, which they can customize with apps, wallpaper, and more. Users can also adjust device settings like WLAN that affect everyone.

When you add a new user, that person needs to set up their space.

Any user can update apps for all other users."</string>
    <string name="print_user_warning">Your device will search for nearby printers over a WLAN connection when you enable the printing service, which will produce WLAN traffic.</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_settings_title_emui">WLAN calling</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_dialog_title">Enable WLAN calling</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_dialog_message">If enabled, you will not be able to place emergency calls through WLAN. Enable?</string>
    <string name="device_name_settings_summary">When you use Bluetooth, WLAN Direct and tethering &amp; portable hotspot, other devices will see this name.</string>
    <string name="device_name_settings_dialog">Modifying the device name will disconnect the current WLAN hotspot connection. Modify it?</string>
    <string name="write_wifi_nfc_tag">Write to WLAN NFC tag</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_smart_switch_title">Smart switching between WLAN and mobile data</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_smart_switch_summary">Evaluate WLAN connectivity and switch between WLAN (may increase traffic) and mobile data to choose the best network connection. Default switch mode is set in mobile network settings</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_smart_switch_summary_global">Evaluate WLAN connectivity and switch between WLAN (may increase traffic) and mobile data to choose the best network connection</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_auto_turn_title">Turn on/off WLAN automatically</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_auto_turn_summary">Turn on WLAN when in range of a known WLAN network and connects to it</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_quality_evaluation_title">Evaluate available WLAN networks</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_quality_evaluation_summary">Evaluate available WLAN networks. Auto-connect is paused for saved networks that have no Internet access</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_fast_connect_title">Optimize login experience for free WLAN hotspots</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_fast_connect_summary">For certain free WLAN hotspots, detect and access the verification code from the incoming SMS verification message and logs in to the network via the browser automatically (currently only supported in Mainland China)</string>
    <string name="link_plus_live_update_description_EMUI_5">When Link+ live update is enabled, your phone automatically updates communication parameters data through your wireless network (WLAN by default) in order to improve relevant communication features.</string>
    <string name="reset_network_desc_summary"><li>WLAN</li>"
"<li>Mobile data</li>"
"<li>Bluetooth</li></string>
    <string name="reset_network_desc_summary_wifi_only"><li>WLAN</li>"
"<li>Bluetooth</li></string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_title_emui_wifionly">Use GPS and WLAN</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_title_emui_wifionly">Use WLAN</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_new_details">"1. WLAN bridge significantly improves the transmission range and intensity of WLAN signals. Other devices can connect to your current WLAN network through your device.
2. WLAN bridge supports access from up to 4 devices.
3. WLAN bridge does not work with the WLAN hotspot and WLAN Direct features. If WLAN bridge is enabled, some apps that use P2P services may not work properly.
4. Using WLAN bridge consumes battery power more quickly.
5. If you receive a message notifying you that WLAN resources are being used by another service, go to Settings > WLAN > WLAN Direct and disconnect any connected devices. Or you can turn WLAN off and then on again to auto-disconnect all devices."</string>
    <string name="wifi_qrcode_share_notice_new">Scan to connect to this WLAN network</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_one">"1. Make sure Access my location is enabled.
2. Select Use GPS, WLAN, and mobile networks in Location mode.
3. Connect to a WLAN hotspot or enable mobile data.
4. Check if the app you are using has access to the Location permission in Phone manager > Permission manager > Access location info.
5. If you have set Location mode as Use GPS only, please make sure you are using location access in an open and unobstructed environment where GPS signals can be received normally.
6. If you are connected to a public hotspot, try turning off WLAN and enabling mobile data. Then try location access again."</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_two">"1. Select Use GPS, WLAN, and mobile networks in Location mode for more accurate location access.
2. If you are using a metal case on your device, remove the case or use a non-metallic case and try again.
3. Check if the app you are using has access to the Location permission in Phone manager > Permission manager > Access location info.
4. Navigation works better in wide, unobstructed areas. Place your phone in a position near the windshield of your vehicle, such as the dashboard or other unobstructed areas in your car."</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_new_details_ex">"%1$d. WLAN bridge significantly improves the transmission range and intensity of WLAN signals. Other devices can connect to your current WLAN network through your device.
%2$d. WLAN bridge supports access from up to %6$d devices.
%3$d. WLAN bridge does not work with the WLAN hotspot and WLAN Direct features. If WLAN bridge is enabled, some apps that use P2P services may not work properly.
%4$d. Using WLAN bridge consumes battery power more quickly.
%5$d. If you receive a message notifying you that WLAN resources are being used by another service, go to Settings > WLAN > WLAN Direct and disconnect any connected devices. Or you can turn WLAN off and then on again to auto-disconnect all devices."</string>
    <string name="wifiap_use_help_details_ex">"%1$d. You can use a portable WLAN hotspot device as your Internet access point. Peripherals can be connected to your device through WLAN and connected devices will access the Internet through the mobile network.
%2$d. Using a portable WLAN hotspot will require your mobile data connection to be enabled, and will consume some data.
%3$d. Using a portable WLAN hotspot may drain your battery faster."</string>
    <string name="wifiap_connect_help_details_open_ex">"Manual connection:
%2$d. Enable WLAN on target device, and find the hotspot %1$s.
%3$d. Connect to hotspot."</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_one_summary">"%1$d. Make sure Access my location is enabled.
%2$d. Select Use GPS, WLAN, and mobile networks in Location mode.
%3$d. Connect to a WLAN hotspot or enable mobile data.
%4$d. Check if the app you are using has access to the Location permission in Phone manager > Permission manager > Access location info.
%5$d. If you have set Location mode as Use GPS only, please make sure you are using location access in an open and unobstructed environment where GPS signals can be received normally.
%6$d. If you are connected to a public hotspot, try turning off WLAN and enabling mobile data. Then try location access again."</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_two_summary">"%1$d. Select Use GPS, WLAN, and mobile networks in Location mode for more accurate location access.
%2$d. If you are using a metal case on your device, remove the case or use a non-metallic case and try again.
%3$d. Check if the app you are using has access to the Location permission in Phone manager > Permission manager > Access location info.
%4$d. Navigation works better in wide, unobstructed areas. Place your phone in a position near the windshield of your vehicle, such as the dashboard or other unobstructed areas in your car."</string>
    <string name="turn_off_data_saver_message">Using a portable hotspot requires disabling Data saver. Disable?</string>
    <string name="first_wlan_hotspot_text">WLAN hotspot lets you share your network connection with others, but may drain battery power faster and increase data usage fees.</string>
    <string name="hotspot_power_notification_title">WLAN hotspot disabled</string>
    <string name="hotspot_power_notification_ticker_text">WLAN hotspot disabled</string>
    <string name="toast_entitle_wifi_need_close">WLAN is connected, forbid to open this function, please close the WLAN.</string>
    <string name="wifi_activated_warning_Title">WLAN turned on</string>
    <string name="wifi_turn_off_warning_message_wifiap">"Mobile hotspot and WLAN can't be turned on at the same time. Turn off WLAN?"</string>
    <string name="wifi_turn_off_warning_message_usb">"WLAN must be turned off now. It will be automatically turned on again once your phone has communicated with AT&amp;T's servers."</string>
    <string name="broadcast_ssid_is_show_dialog">If you turn off Broadcast network name (SSID) option, your phone will not be visible to other devices and will not appear in the list of available WLAN networks. Other devices can still connect to your hotspot by entering your network name manually.</string>
    <string name="enable">Auto-connection to AT&amp;T WLAN enabled</string>
    <string name="disable">Auto-connection to AT&amp;T WLAN disabled</string>
    <string name="auto_connect_wifi_suggestion">Restart WLAN for the Auto-connection settings to take effect.</string>
    <string name="wifi_network_detect_summary">Check for Internet accessibility when connecting to a WLAN hotspot</string>
    <string name="wifi_disable_by_deivice_admin">WLAN has been disabled by the device administrator</string>
    <string name="wifi_required_info_text">To complete the setup, your tablet needs access to a WLAN network. Once setup is complete, you can switch between mobile data and WLAN.</string>
    <string name="wifi_setting_frequency_band_title">WLAN frequency band</string>
    <string name="wifi_alert_lockdown_by_device_owner">%1$s manages your device and doesn’t allow you to modify or delete this WLAN network. For more information, contact your administrator.</string>
</resources>
