<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="connected_via_wfa">[Çöññéçţéð Vîå ŴĻÅÑ åššîšţåñţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_off">[ŴĻÅÑ öƒƒ. one two]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_no_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ ðîšçöññéçţéð. one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_one_bar">[ŴĻÅÑ öñé ɓåŕ. one two]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_two_bars">[ŴĻÅÑ ţŵö ɓåŕš. one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_three_bars">[ŴĻÅÑ ţĥŕéé ɓåŕš. one two three]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_wifi_signal_full">[ŴĻÅÑ šîĝñåļ ƒûļļ. one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_verbose_logging">[Éñåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ Véŕɓöšé ļöĝĝîñĝ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_aggressive_handover">[ÅĝĝŕéššîVé ŴĻÅÑ ţö çéļļûļåŕ ĥåñðöVéŕ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_allow_scan_with_traffic">[Åļŵåýš åļļöŵ ŴĻÅÑ ŕöåḿîñĝ šçåñš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_verbose_logging_summary">[Îñçŕéåšé ŴĻÅÑ ļöĝĝîñĝ ļéVéļ åñð šĥöŵ þéŕ ŠŠÎÐ ŔŠŠÎ îñ ŴĻÅÑ þîçķéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_aggressive_handover_summary">[Ŵĥéñ éñåɓļéð, ŴĻÅÑ ŵîļļ ɓé ḿöŕé åĝĝŕéššîVé îñ ĥåñðîñĝ öVéŕ ţĥé ðåţå çöññéçţîöñ ţö çéļļûļåŕ ŵĥéñ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ šîĝñåļ îš ļöŵ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="wifi_allow_scan_with_traffic_summary">[Åļļöŵ/Ŕéšţŕîçţ ŴĻÅÑ ŕöåḿîñĝ šçåñš ɓåšéð öñ ţĥé åḿöûñţ öƒ ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç þŕéšéñţ åţ ţĥé îñţéŕƒåçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="mobile_data_always_on_summary">[Åļŵåýš ķééþ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå åçţîVé, éVéñ ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îš åçţîVé (ƒöŕ ƒåšţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ) one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="radio_controls_summary">[Ḿåñåĝé ŴĻÅÑ, βļûéţööţĥ, åîŕþļåñé ḿöðé, ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš, &amp; νÞÑš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="wifi_assistant_title">[ŴĻÅÑ Åššîšţåñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_quick_toggle_title">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_quick_toggle_summary">[Ţûŕñ öñ ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings_category">[ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_wizard_title">[Šéļéçţ ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_select_network">[Šéļéçţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_starting">[Ţûŕñîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ öñ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_stopping">[Ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_poor_network_detection_summary">[ÅVöîð çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš ŵîţĥ þööŕ çöññéçţîVîţý one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_automatically_connect_title">[Åûţö-ûšé öþéñ ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_automatically_connect_summary">[Ļéţ ŴĻÅÑ åššîšţåñţ åûţö-çöññéçţ ţö öþéñ ñéţŵöŕķš ŵîţĥ ĝööð Îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_notify_text">[Ţö îḿþŕöVé ļöçåţîöñ åççûŕåçý, šýšţéḿ åþþš åñð šéŕVîçéš çåñ šţîļļ šçåñ ƒöŕ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš. Ýöû çåñ çĥåñĝé ţĥîš îñ LINK_BEGINšçåññîñĝ šéţţîñĝšLINK_END. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setting_sleep_policy_title">[Ķééþ ŴĻÅÑ öñ ðûŕîñĝ šļééþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_suspend_optimizations">[ŴĻÅÑ öþţîḿîžåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_suspend_optimizations_summary">[Ḿîñîḿîžé ɓåţţéŕý ûšåĝé ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îš öñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_access_points">[ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_menu_p2p">[ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_wifi_off">[Ţö šéé åVåîļåɓļé ñéţŵöŕķš, ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ öñ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_wifi_on">[Šéåŕçĥîñĝ ƒöŕ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_user_restricted">"[Ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåVé þéŕḿîššîöñ ţö çĥåñĝé ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_setup_title">[ŴĻÅÑ Þŕöţéçţéð Šéţûþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_onstart_pbc">[Þŕéšš ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ Þŕöţéçţéð Šéţûþ ɓûţţöñ öñ ýöûŕ ŕöûţéŕ. Îţ ḿåý ɓé çåļļéð \"ŴÞŠ\" öŕ çöñţåîñ ţĥîš šýḿɓöļ: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_onstart_pin">[Éñţéŕ þîñ %1$s öñ ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ ŕöûţéŕ. Ţĥé šéţûþ çåñ ţåķé ûþ ţö ţŵö ḿîñûţéš ţö çöḿþļéţé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_connected">[Çöññéçţéð ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_always_turnon_message">"[Ţö îḿþŕöVé ļöçåţîöñ åççûŕåçý åñð ƒöŕ öţĥéŕ þûŕþöšéš, %1$s ŵåñţš ţö ţûŕñ öñ ñéţŵöŕķ šçåññîñĝ, éVéñ ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îš öƒƒ.

Åļļöŵ ţĥîš ƒöŕ åļļ åþþš ţĥåţ ŵåñţ ţö šçåñ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_skipped_message">"[ŴÅŔÑÎÑĜ: Ýöû ḿåý îñçûŕ éхţŕå çåŕŕîéŕ ðåţå ƒééš.

Þĥöñé šéţûþ ḿåý ŕéQûîŕé šîĝñîƒîçåñţ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîVîţý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_and_mobile_skipped_message">"[ŴÅŔÑÎÑĜ: Ţĥé þĥöñé ŵöñ'ţ ɓé åɓļé ţö Véŕîƒý ţĥåţ ýöûŕ šöƒţŵåŕé îš ûþ ţö ðåţé. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_connect_failed_message">[Ţĥé þĥöñé ŵåš ûñåɓļé ţö çöññéçţ ţö ţĥîš ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wifi_advanced_titlebar">[ÅðVåñçéð ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_configure_titlebar">[Çöñƒîĝûŕé ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_advanced_not_available">[ŴĻÅÑ åðVåñçéð šéţţîñĝš åŕé ñöţ åVåîļåɓļé ƒöŕ ţĥîš ûšéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_checkbox_text">[Þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_failed_subtext">[Þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ éŕŕöŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_ap_text">[Çöñƒîĝûŕé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_subtext">[%1$s %2$s þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_suggestion_title">[Éñåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_suggestion_summary">[Ûšé ŴĻÅÑ îñšţéåð öƒ ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_mode_title">[ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_mode_dialog_title">[ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ ḿöðé one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_off_explanation">[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ îš öñ, ýöûŕ þĥöñé çåñ ŕöûţé çåļļš Vîå ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš öŕ ýöûŕ çåŕŕîéŕ’š ñéţŵöŕķ, ðéþéñðîñĝ öñ ýöûŕ þŕéƒéŕéñçé åñð ŵĥîçĥ šîĝñåļ îš šţŕöñĝéŕ. βéƒöŕé ţûŕñîñĝ öñ ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé, çĥéçķ ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ çåŕŕîéŕ ŕéĝåŕðîñĝ ƒééš åñð öţĥéŕ ðéţåîļš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]</string>
    <string name="status_wifi_mac_address">[ŴĻÅÑ ḾÅÇ åððŕéšš one two three]</string>
    <string name="reset_network_desc">"[Ţĥîš ŵîļļ ŕéšéţ åļļ ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš, îñçļûðîñĝ:

"<li>ŴĻÅÑ</li>"
"<li>Ḿöɓîļé ðåţå</li>"
"<li>βļûéţööţĥ</li> one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="network_scorer_change_active_dialog_title">[Çĥåñĝé ŴĻÅÑ åššîšţåñţ¿ one two three]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_description">[Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš ţö éšţîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_description">[Ûšé ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš ţö éšţîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="location_scanning_wifi_always_scanning_title">[ŴĻÅÑ šçåññîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="location_scanning_wifi_always_scanning_description">[ÎḿþŕöVé ļöçåţîöñ ɓý åļļöŵîñĝ šýšţéḿ åþþš åñð šéŕVîçéš ţö ðéţéçţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš åţ åñý ţîḿé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="location_network_based">[ŴĻÅÑ &amp; ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ ļöçåţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="location_neighborhood_level">[Ļéţ åþþš ûšé ðåţå ƒŕöḿ šöûŕçéš šûçĥ åš ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš ţö ðéţéŕḿîñé ýöûŕ åþþŕöхîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="location_neighborhood_level_wifi">[Ļöçåţîöñ ðéţéŕḿîñéð ɓý ŴĻÅÑ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="battery_stats_wifi_running_label">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_on_time">[ŴĻÅÑ öñ ţîḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_on_time">[ŴĻÅÑ öñ ţîḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="power_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="usage_type_wifi_running">[ŴĻÅÑ ŕûññîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="usage_type_data_wifi_send">[ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå šéñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="usage_type_data_wifi_recv">[ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ŕéçéîVéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="battery_action_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="battery_desc_wifi">[βåţţéŕý ûšéð ɓý ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="battery_sugg_wifi">"[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ ñöţ ûšîñĝ îţ öŕ ŵĥéñ îţ îšñ'ţ åVåîļåɓļé one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="gadget_toggle_wifi">[Ûþðåţîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="gadget_state_template">[%1$s %2$s one]</string>
    <string name="gadget_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="backup_data_summary">[βåçķ ûþ åþþ ðåţå, ŴĻÅÑ þåššŵöŕðš, åñð öţĥéŕ šéţţîñĝš ţö Ĝööĝļé šéŕVéŕš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="backup_erase_dialog_message">[Šţöþ ɓåçķîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ þåššŵöŕðš, ɓööķḿåŕķš, öţĥéŕ šéţţîñĝš, åñð åþþ ðåţå, þļûš éŕåšé åļļ çöþîéš öñ Ĝööĝļé šéŕVéŕš¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]</string>
    <string name="fullbackup_erase_dialog_message">[Šţöþ ɓåçķîñĝ ûþ ðéVîçé ðåţå (šûçĥ åš ŴĻÅÑ þåššŵöŕðš åñð çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý) åñð åþþ ðåţå (šûçĥ åš šéţţîñĝš åñð ƒîļéš šţöŕéð ɓý åþþš), åñð éŕåšé åļļ çöþîéš öñ Ĝööĝļé ÐŕîVé¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="fullbackup_data_summary">"[Åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ɓåçķ ûþ ðéVîçé ðåţå (šûçĥ åš ŴĻÅÑ þåššŵöŕðš åñð çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý) åñð åþþ ðåţå (šûçĥ åš šéţţîñĝš åñð ƒîļéš šţöŕéð ɓý åþþš) ŕéḿöţéļý.

Ŵĥéñ ýöû ţûŕñ öñ åûţöḿåţîç ɓåçķûþ, ðéVîçé åñð åþþ ðåţå îš þéŕîöðîçåļļý šåVéð ŕéḿöţéļý. Åþþ ðåţå çåñ ɓé åñý ðåţå ţĥåţ åñ åþþ ĥåš šåVéð (ɓåšéð öñ ðéVéļöþéŕ šéţţîñĝš), îñçļûðîñĝ þöţéñţîåļļý šéñšîţîVé ðåţå šûçĥ åš çöñţåçţš, ḿéššåĝéš, åñð þĥöţöš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title">[ŴĻÅÑ šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_editing_network">[Çöññéçţ ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_connecting_network">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_eap_not_supported">"[Ýöû çåñ'ţ çöñƒîĝûŕé åñ ÉÅÞ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîöñ ðûŕîñĝ šéţûþ. Åƒţéŕ šéţûþ, ýöû çåñ ðö ţĥåţ îñ Šéţţîñĝš > Ŵîŕéļéšš &amp; ñéţŵöŕķš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_description_connected">[Ţöûçĥ <b>Ñéхţ</b>" ţö çöñţîñûé ŵîţĥ šéţûþ.

Ţöûçĥ "<b>βåçķ</b> ţö çöññéçţ ţö å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_menu_show_wifi">[Šĥöŵ ŴĻÅÑ ûšåĝé one two three]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_menu_hide_wifi">[Ĥîðé ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_disable_wifi_limit">[Šéţ ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ļîḿîţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_tab_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_app_restrict_background_summary">[Ðîšåɓļé ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ðåţå öñ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķ öñļý. ŴĻÅÑ ŵîļļ ɓé ûšéð îƒ åVåîļåɓļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_app_restrict_dialog">"[Ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé ḿåý çåûšé åñ åþþ ţĥåţ ðéþéñðš öñ ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ðåţå ţö šţöþ ŵöŕķîñĝ ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îšñ'ţ åVåîļåɓļé.

Çĥéçķ šéţţîñĝš ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé åþþ ţö šéé îƒ ţĥéŕé åŕé ḿöŕé åþþŕöþŕîåţé ðåţå ûšåĝé çöñţŕöļš åVåîļåɓļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="data_usage_restrict_background">"[Îƒ ýöû ŕéšţŕîçţ ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå, šöḿé åþþš åñð šéŕVîçéš ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ûñļéšš ýöû'ŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="data_usage_restrict_background_multiuser">"[Îƒ ýöû ŕéšţŕîçţ ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå, šöḿé åþþš åñð šéŕVîçéš ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ûñļéšš ýöû'ŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ.

Ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ åƒƒéçţš åļļ ûšéŕš öñ ţĥîš þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_body">[Šéļéçţ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥåţ åŕé ḿöɓîļé ĥöţšþöţš. Åþþš çåñ ɓé ŕéšţŕîçţéð ƒŕöḿ ûšîñĝ ţĥéšé ñéţŵöŕķš ŵĥéñ ŕûññîñĝ îñ ţĥé ɓåçķĝŕöûñð. Åþþš ḿåý åļšö ĝéñéŕåţé ŵåŕñîñĝš ŵĥéñ ûšîñĝ ţĥéšé ñéţŵöŕķš ƒöŕ ļåŕĝé ðöŵñļöåðš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_wifi_disabled">[Ţö šéļéçţ ḿöɓîļé ĥöţšþöţš, ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ öñ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="user_add_user_message_long">"[Ýöû çåñ šĥåŕé ţĥîš ðéVîçé ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þéöþļé ɓý çŕéåţîñĝ åððîţîöñåļ ûšéŕš. Éåçĥ ûšéŕ ĥåš ţĥéîŕ öŵñ šþåçé, ŵĥîçĥ ţĥéý çåñ çûšţöḿîžé ŵîţĥ ţĥéîŕ öŵñ åþþš, ŵåļļþåþéŕ, åñð šö öñ. Ûšéŕš çåñ åļšö åðĵûšţ ţåɓļéţ šéţţîñĝš ļîķé ŴĻÅÑ ţĥåţ åƒƒéçţ éVéŕýöñé.

Åƒţéŕ ýöû çŕéåţé å ñéŵ ûšéŕ, ţĥåţ þéŕšöñ ñééðš ţö ĝö ţĥŕöûĝĥ å šéţûþ þŕöçéšš.

Åñý ûšéŕ çåñ åççéþţ ûþðåţéð åþþ þéŕḿîššîöñš öñ ɓéĥåļƒ öƒ åļļ öţĥéŕ ûšéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="restriction_wifi_config_title">[ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå one two three]</string>
    <string name="restriction_wifi_config_summary">[Åļļöŵ ḿöðîƒîçåţîöñ öƒ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="keywords_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="keywords_wifi_calling">[ŴĻÅÑ ŴĻÅÑ çåļļ çåļļîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_wifi_nfc_tag">[Šéţ ûþ ŴĻÅÑ ÑFÇ ţåĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="condition_hotspot_summary">[Þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ %1$s îš åçţîVé. ŴĻÅÑ ƒöŕ ţĥîš ðéVîçé ĥåš ɓééñ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="condition_airplane_summary">"[ŴĻÅÑ, βļûéţööţĥ, åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķ åŕé ţûŕñéð öƒƒ. Ýöû çåñ'ţ ḿåķé þĥöñé çåļļš öŕ çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé Îñţéŕñéţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="condition_cellular_summary">[Îñţéŕñéţ îš åVåîļåɓļé öñļý Vîå ŴĻÅÑ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="condition_bg_data_summary">[βåçķĝŕöûñð ðåţå îš öñļý åVåîļåɓļé Vîå ŴĻÅÑ. Ţĥîš ḿåý åƒƒéçţ šöḿé åþþš öŕ šéŕVîçéš ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îš ñöţ åVåîļåɓļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_bridge_checkbox_text">[ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_bridge_tittle_text">[ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_bridge_text">[Çöñƒîĝûŕé ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_settings_summary">[Šéţ ţĥé ɓŕîðĝé ñåḿé, þåššŵöŕð, åñð ḿöŕé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_title">[Ĥéļþ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_details">"[1. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé çåñ šîĝñîƒîçåñţļý îḿþŕöVé ţĥé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ ŕåñĝé åñð îñţéñšîţý öƒ ŴĻÅÑ šîĝñåļš. Öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš çåñ ɓé çöññéçţéð ţö ýöûŕ çûŕŕéñţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ţĥŕöûĝĥ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé.
2. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé šûþþöŕţš åççéšš ƒŕöḿ ûþ ţö 4 ðéVîçéš.
3. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé ðöéš ñöţ ŵöŕķ ŵîţĥ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ åñð ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ ƒéåţûŕéš. Îƒ ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé îš éñåɓļéð, šöḿé åþþļîçåţîöñš ţĥåţ ûšé Þ2Þ šéŕVîçéš ḿåý ñöţ ŵöŕķ þŕöþéŕļý.
4. Ûšîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé çöñšûḿéš ýöûŕ ɓåţţéŕý þöŵéŕ ƒåšţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_switch_nowifi_summary">[ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîöñ ŕéQûîŕéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_switch_wifi_summary">[Šĥåŕé çöññéçţéð ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_connected_network_Toast">[Çöññéçţéð ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s one two three four]</string>
    <string name="huawei_beam_explained">[Ĥûåŵéî βéåḿ ļéţš ýöû ţŕåñšƒéŕ ƒîļéš, šûçĥ åš þîçţûŕéš, Vîðéöš, çöñţåçţš åñð ÛŔĻš, ɓéţŵééñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð åñöţĥéŕ ÑFÇ-çåþåɓļé ðéVîçé. Ĥûåŵéî βéåḿ îš åçţîVåţéð ɓý þļåçîñĝ ţĥé ţŵö ðéVîçéš çļöšé ţöĝéţĥéŕ (ûšûåļļý ɓåçķ ţö ɓåçķ) åñð ţåþþîñĝ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ. Þļéåšé ñöţé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ βļûéţööţĥ öŕ ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ţûŕñéð öñ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ɓéƒöŕé ƒîļé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_display_settings_summary">[Ðîšþļåý ýöûŕ þĥöñé šçŕééñ öñ åñöţĥéŕ ðîšþļåý öVéŕ å ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="advanced_wifi_settings_title">[ÅðVåñçéð šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="huawei_beam_front_explained">"[Ĥûåŵéî βéåḿ ļéţš ýöû ţŕåñšƒéŕ ƒîļéš ţö öţĥéŕ ÑFÇ ðéVîçéš ɓý þļåçîñĝ ţĥé ðéVîçéš çļöšé ţöĝéţĥéŕ. Föŕ éхåḿþļé, ýöû çåñ ŵîŕéļéššļý ţŕåñšƒéŕ þîçţûŕéš, Vîðéöš, çöñţåçţš, ÛŔĻš, åñð ḿöŕé ɓéţŵééñ ţŵö ÑFÇ-çåþåɓļé ðéVîçéš. Šîḿþļý:
1. Þļåçé ţĥé ƒŕöñţ þåñéļ öƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åĝåîñšţ åñöţĥéŕ ÑFÇ ðéVîçé, åñð þîçķ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åƒţéŕ ýöû ĥéåŕ å ţöñé.
2. Ţöûçĥ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ ŵîţĥîñ ţĥŕéé šéçöñðš öƒ ĥéåŕîñĝ ţĥé ţöñé.
3. Þļåçé ţĥé ƒŕöñţ þåñéļ öƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åĝåîñšţ ţĥé öţĥéŕ ÑFÇ ðéVîçé åĝåîñ ţö çöḿþļéţé ţĥé ţŕåñšƒéŕ. Þļéåšé ñöţé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ βļûéţööţĥ öŕ ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ţûŕñéð öñ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ɓéƒöŕé ƒîļé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="wifiap_use_help_details">"[1. Ýöû çåñ ûšé å þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ðéVîçé åš ýöûŕ Îñţéŕñéţ åççéšš þöîñţ. Þéŕîþĥéŕåļš çåñ ɓé çöññéçţéð ţö ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ţĥŕöûĝĥ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ åñð çöññéçţéð ðéVîçéš ŵîļļ åççéšš ţĥé Îñţéŕñéţ ţĥŕöûĝĥ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ.
2. Ûšîñĝ å þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ŵîļļ ŕéQûîŕé ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå çöññéçţîöñ ţö ɓé öñ, åñð ŵîļļ çöñšûḿé šöḿé ðåţå ţŕåƒƒîç.
3. Ûšîñĝ å þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ḿåý ðŕåîñ ýöûŕ ɓåţţéŕý ļîƒé ƒåšţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="wifiap_connect_help_details_open">"[Ḿåñûåļ çöññéçţîöñ:
1. Ţûŕñ öñ ŴĻÅÑ öñ ţĥé ţåŕĝéţ ðéVîçé, åñð ƒîñð ţĥé ĥöţšþöţ %1$s.
2. Çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé ĥöţšþöţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_title">[Çĥîñå Ḿöɓîļé ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_warning">[Ýöû åŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å Çĥîñå Ḿöɓîļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. Ûšîñĝ ţĥîš ñéţŵöŕķ ḿåý þŕöðûçé åþþļîçåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ûšåĝé ƒééš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_never_notify">[Ðö ñöţ ŕéḿîñð åĝåîñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_notify_switch">[Çĥîñå Ḿöɓîļé ŴĻÅÑ ŕéḿîñðéŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_connected_to_cmcc_notify_summary">"[Ŕéḿîñð ḿé ŵĥéñ Î'ḿ çöññéçţéð ţö å Çĥîñå Ḿöɓîļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_cmcc_no_notification_summary">[Ðö ñöţ ðîšþļåý åñý ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš ŵĥéñ šŵîţçĥîñĝ ñéţŵöŕķš (ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ţö ŴĻÅÑ åñð Vîçé Véŕšå, öŕ ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš) one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_description_wifionly">[Ûšé ĜÞŠ åñð ŴĻÅÑ ţö éšţîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_description_wifionly">[Ûšé ŴĻÅÑ ţö éšţîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_title">[ŴĻÅÑ+ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_summary">[Îñţéļļîĝéñţļý šéļéçţ ŴĻÅÑ öŕ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description">"[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ+ îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý ŵîļļ ɓé éVåļûåţéð ţö þŕöVîðé šḿåŕţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ (ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ûšåĝé ḿåý îñçŕéåšé). ŴĻÅÑ+ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý:
1. Šŵîţçĥéš ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå (ŵîţĥ ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš) ţö þŕöVîðé å šḿööţĥ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé.
2. Ţûŕñš öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ+ šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_intelligent_switch_description">[Îñţéļļîĝéñţļý šŵîţçĥ ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķš ƒöŕ å ɓéţţéŕ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_auto_turn_on_description">[Åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ţûŕñ öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ ýöû åþþŕöåçĥ å ķñöŵñ ļöçåţîöñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_global_description">"[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ+ îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý ŵîļļ ɓé éVåļûåţéð ţö þŕöVîðé šḿåŕţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ (ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ûšåĝé ḿåý îñçŕéåšé). ŴĻÅÑ+ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý:
1. Šŵîţçĥéš ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ţö þŕöVîðé å šḿööţĥ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé.
2. Ţûŕñš öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_title_emui">[Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ, åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_title_emui">[Ûšé ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="pgps_switch_title">[ĜÞŠ åççéļéŕåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="pgps_switch_summary">[Åļļöŵ ĜÞŠ ţö çöļļéçţ ñéåŕɓý çéļļûļåŕ ɓåšé šţåţîöñ åñð ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ţö þŕöVîðé Qûîçķéŕ åñð ḿöŕé åççûŕåţé ļöçåţîöñ šéŕVîçéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="find_no_wlan_ap">[Ûñåɓļé ţö ƒîñð ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="cannot_connect_wlan">[Ûñåɓļé ţö çöññéçţ ţö ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="cannot_login_internet_with_wlan">[Ûñåɓļé ţö åççéšš Îñţéŕñéţ öVéŕ ŴĻÅÑ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wfd_connect_fail">[ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ çöññéçţîöñ ƒåîļéð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="find_no_wfd_device">[Ûñåɓļé ţö ƒîñð ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ ðéVîçé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wfd_search_no_devices_causes">"[Ñö åVåîļåɓļé ðéVîçéš ƒöûñð, îţ ḿåý ɓé ţĥåţ:
1. Ţĥé þåîŕéð ðéVîçé îš ñöţ ðîšçöVéŕåɓļé.
2. Ţĥé þåîŕéð ðéVîçé îš éхþéŕîéñçîñĝ ţéçĥñîçåļ îššûéš. Ţŕý ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ŕé-öþéñ ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ.
3. Ýöûŕ öŵñ ðéVîçé îš éхþéŕîéñçîñĝ ţéçĥñîçåļ îššûéš. Ţŕý ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ŕé-öþéñ ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="wfd_connected_failed_causes">"[Ţĥé çöññéçţîöñ çöûļð ñöţ ɓé éšţåɓļîšĥéð. Þöššîɓļé ŕéåšöñš:
1. Ţĥé þåîŕéð ðéVîçé ðîðñ'ţ åççéþţ ţĥé çöññéçţîöñ ŕéQûéšţ.
2. Éîţĥéŕ ðéVîçé ĥåš åļŕéåðý éšţåɓļîšĥéð åñöţĥéŕ ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ çöññéçţîöñ.
3. Ţĥé þåîŕéð ðéVîçé îš éхþéŕîéñçîñĝ ţéçĥñîçåļ îššûéš. Ţŕý ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_qrcode_share_notice">[Šçåñ ţĥé qŔ çöðé ţö çöññéçţ ţö ţĥîš ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="devices_not_found_solution_title">"[Îƒ ţĥé ðéVîçé çåñ'ţ ɓé ƒöûñð, ţŕý ţĥé ƒöļļöŵîñĝ: one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="devices_not_found_solution_message">"[1. Ḿåķé šûŕé ţĥé ðéVîçé îš šçåññîñĝ ƒöŕ öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš.
2. Îƒ ţĥé þééŕ ðéVîçé îš éхþéŕîéñçîñĝ îššûéš, ŕéšţåŕţ ŴĻÅÑ åñð åççéšš ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ åĝåîñ.
3. Îƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé îš éхþéŕîéñçîñĝ îššûéš, ŕéšţåŕţ ŴĻÅÑ åñð åççéšš ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="devices_not_connected_solution_message">"[1. Ḿåķé šûŕé ţĥåţ ţĥé þééŕ ðéVîçé ĥåš åççéþţéð ţĥé çöññéçţîöñ ŕéQûéšţ.
2. Ḿåķé šûŕé ɓöţĥ ðéVîçéš ĥåVé ñöţ çöññéçţéð ţö öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš.
3. Îƒ ţĥé þééŕ ðéVîçé îš éхþéŕîéñçîñĝ îššûéš, ţŕý ŕéçöññéçţîñĝ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description_emui">"[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ+ îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý ŵîļļ ɓé éVåļûåţéð ţö þŕöVîðé šḿåŕţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ (ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ûšåĝé ḿåý îñçŕéåšé). ŴĻÅÑ+ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý:
1. Šŵîţçĥéš ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå (Ýöû çåñ šéļéçţ ţĥé ðéƒåûļţ šŵîţçĥîñĝ ḿöðé îñ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš) ţö þŕöVîðé å šḿööţĥ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé.
2. Ţûŕñš öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="link_plus_live_update_description">[Ŵĥéñ Ļîñķ+ ļîVé ûþðåţé îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ þĥöñé åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ûþðåţéš ţĥé ðåţå öƒ çöḿḿûñîçåţîöñ þåŕåḿéţéŕš ţĥŕöûĝĥ ýöûŕ ŵîŕéļéšš ñéţŵöŕķ (ŴĻÅÑ ɓý ðéƒåûļţ) îñ öŕðéŕ ţö îḿþŕöVé ŕéļéVåñţ Ļîñķ+ ƒéåţûŕéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description_emui2">"[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ+ îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý ŵîļļ ɓé éVåļûåţéð ţö þŕöVîðé šḿåŕţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ (ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ûšåĝé ḿåý îñçŕéåšé). ŴĻÅÑ+ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý:
1. Šŵîţçĥéš ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå (Ýöû çåñ šéļéçţ ţĥé ðéƒåûļţ šŵîţçĥîñĝ ḿöðé îñ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš) ţö þŕöVîðé å šḿööţĥ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé.
2. Ţûŕñš öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ.
3. ÉVåļûåţéš åVåîļåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš. ÐéVîçé ŵîļļ ñöţ åûţö-çöññéçţ ţö šåVéð ñéţŵöŕķš ŵîţĥöûţ åñ Îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ.
4. Föŕ šöḿé ƒŕéé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţš, öɓţåîñš ţĥé Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé ƒŕöḿ ţĥé îñçöḿîñĝ ŠḾŠ ḿéššåĝé åñð ļöĝš îñţö ţĥé ñéţŵöŕķ Vîå ţĥé ɓŕöŵšéŕ (çûŕŕéñţļý öñļý šûþþöŕţéð îñ Çĥîñå). one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_global_description2">"[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ+ îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý ŵîļļ ɓé éVåļûåţéð ţö þŕöVîðé šḿåŕţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ (ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ûšåĝé ḿåý îñçŕéåšé). ŴĻÅÑ+ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý:
1. Šŵîţçĥéš ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ţö þŕöVîðé å šḿööţĥ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé.
2. Ţûŕñš öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ.
3. ÉVåļûåţéš åVåîļåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš. ÐéVîçé ŵîļļ ñöţ åûţö-çöññéçţ ţö šåVéð ñéţŵöŕķš ŵîţĥöûţ åñ Îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="help_message">"[1. Ýöûŕ þŕîñţéŕ åñð þĥöñé åŕéñ'ţ çöññéçţéð ţö ţĥé šåḿé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ.
2. Ýöûŕ þŕîñţéŕ ðöéšñ'ţ šûþþöŕţ ţĥîš þåŕţîçûļåŕ þŕîñţîñĝ šéŕVîçé (çöñƒîŕḿ ŵîţĥ ḿåñûƒåçţûŕéŕ).
3. Šéåŕçĥîñĝ ĥåš ţîḿéð öûţ. Ţŕý åĝåîñ îƒ ţĥîš îš ţĥé çåšé.
4. Ýöûŕ þŕîñţéŕ ĥåš çŕåšĥéð. Ŕéšţåŕţ ýöûŕ þŕîñţéŕ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_cloud_security_check_title">[ŴĻÅÑ šéçûŕîţý çĥéçķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_cloud_security_check_summary">[Çĥéçķ ţĥé šéçûŕîţý ļéVéļ öƒ çöññéçţéð ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥŕöûĝĥ Þĥöñé Ḿåñåĝéŕ, åñð þåûšé åûţö-çöññéçţ ţö šåVéð ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥåţ þöšé šéçûŕîţý ŕîšķš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_description_emui3">"[Ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ+ îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý ŵîļļ ɓé éVåļûåţéð ţö þŕöVîðé šḿåŕţ ñéţŵöŕķ šŵîţçĥîñĝ, åñð îţ ŵîļļ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ûþðåţé ţĥé öþţîḿîžåţîöñ þåŕåḿéţéŕš ţĥŕöûĝĥ ŴĻÅÑ (ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ûšåĝé ḿåý îñçŕéåšé). ŴĻÅÑ+ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý:
1. Šŵîţçĥéš ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå (Ýöû çåñ šéļéçţ ţĥé ðéƒåûļţ šŵîţçĥîñĝ ḿöðé îñ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš) ţö þŕöVîðé å šḿööţĥ Îñţéŕñéţ éхþéŕîéñçé.
2. Ţûŕñš öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ.
3. ÉVåļûåţéš åVåîļåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš. Föŕ šåVéð ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥåţ ĥåVé ñö Îñţéŕñéţ åççéšš, åûţö-çöññéçţ îš þåûšéð.
4. Föŕ çéŕţåîñ ƒŕéé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţš, ðéţéçţš åñð åççéššéš ţĥé Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé ƒŕöḿ ţĥé îñçöḿîñĝ ŠḾŠ Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ ḿéššåĝé åñð ļöĝš îñţö ţĥé ñéţŵöŕķ Vîå ţĥé ɓŕöŵšéŕ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý (çûŕŕéñţļý öñļý šûþþöŕţéð îñ Çĥîñå). one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="user_add_user_message">"[Ýöû çåñ šĥåŕé ţĥîš ðéVîçé ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þéöþļé ɓý çŕéåţîñĝ åððîţîöñåļ ûšéŕš. Éåçĥ ûšéŕ ĥåš ţĥéîŕ öŵñ šþåçé, ŵĥîçĥ ţĥéý çåñ çûšţöḿîžé ŵîţĥ åþþš, ŵåļļþåþéŕ, åñð ḿöŕé. Ûšéŕš çåñ åļšö åðĵûšţ ðéVîçé šéţţîñĝš ļîķé ŴĻÅÑ ţĥåţ åƒƒéçţ éVéŕýöñé.

Ŵĥéñ ýöû åðð å ñéŵ ûšéŕ, ţĥåţ þéŕšöñ ñééðš ţö šéţ ûþ ţĥéîŕ šþåçé.

Åñý ûšéŕ çåñ ûþðåţé åþþš ƒöŕ åļļ öţĥéŕ ûšéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="print_user_warning">[Ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ŵîļļ šéåŕçĥ ƒöŕ ñéåŕɓý þŕîñţéŕš öVéŕ å ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîöñ ŵĥéñ ýöû éñåɓļé ţĥé þŕîñţîñĝ šéŕVîçé, ŵĥîçĥ ŵîļļ þŕöðûçé ŴĻÅÑ ţŕåƒƒîç. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_settings_title_emui">[ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_dialog_title">[Éñåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ çåļļîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_dialog_message">[Îƒ éñåɓļéð, ýöû ŵîļļ ñöţ ɓé åɓļé ţö þļåçé éḿéŕĝéñçý çåļļš ţĥŕöûĝĥ ŴĻÅÑ. Éñåɓļé¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="device_name_settings_summary">[Ŵĥéñ ýöû ûšé βļûéţööţĥ, ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ åñð ţéţĥéŕîñĝ &amp; þöŕţåɓļé ĥöţšþöţ, öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš ŵîļļ šéé ţĥîš ñåḿé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="device_name_settings_dialog">[Ḿöðîƒýîñĝ ţĥé ðéVîçé ñåḿé ŵîļļ ðîšçöññéçţ ţĥé çûŕŕéñţ ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ çöññéçţîöñ. Ḿöðîƒý îţ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="write_wifi_nfc_tag">[Ŵŕîţé ţö ŴĻÅÑ ÑFÇ ţåĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_smart_switch_title">[Šḿåŕţ šŵîţçĥîñĝ ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_smart_switch_summary">[ÉVåļûåţé ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý åñð šŵîţçĥ ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ (ḿåý îñçŕéåšé ţŕåƒƒîç) åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ţö çĥööšé ţĥé ɓéšţ ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ. Ðéƒåûļţ šŵîţçĥ ḿöðé îš šéţ îñ ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ šéţţîñĝš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_smart_switch_summary_global">[ÉVåļûåţé ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîVîţý åñð šŵîţçĥ ɓéţŵééñ ŴĻÅÑ (ḿåý îñçŕéåšé ţŕåƒƒîç) åñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ţö çĥööšé ţĥé ɓéšţ ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_auto_turn_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ/öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_auto_turn_summary">[Ţûŕñ öñ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ îñ ŕåñĝé öƒ å ķñöŵñ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ åñð çöññéçţš ţö îţ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_quality_evaluation_title">[ÉVåļûåţé åVåîļåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_quality_evaluation_summary">[ÉVåļûåţé åVåîļåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš. Åûţö-çöññéçţ îš þåûšéð ƒöŕ šåVéð ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥåţ ĥåVé ñö Îñţéŕñéţ åççéšš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_fast_connect_title">[Öþţîḿîžé ļöĝîñ éхþéŕîéñçé ƒöŕ ƒŕéé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wifi_plus_fast_connect_summary">[Föŕ çéŕţåîñ ƒŕéé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţš, ðéţéçţ åñð åççéšš ţĥé Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ çöðé ƒŕöḿ ţĥé îñçöḿîñĝ ŠḾŠ Véŕîƒîçåţîöñ ḿéššåĝé åñð ļöĝš îñ ţö ţĥé ñéţŵöŕķ Vîå ţĥé ɓŕöŵšéŕ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý (çûŕŕéñţļý öñļý šûþþöŕţéð îñ Ḿåîñļåñð Çĥîñå) one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="link_plus_live_update_description_EMUI_5">[Ŵĥéñ Ļîñķ+ ļîVé ûþðåţé îš éñåɓļéð, ýöûŕ þĥöñé åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ûþðåţéš çöḿḿûñîçåţîöñ þåŕåḿéţéŕš ðåţå ţĥŕöûĝĥ ýöûŕ ŵîŕéļéšš ñéţŵöŕķ (ŴĻÅÑ ɓý ðéƒåûļţ) îñ öŕðéŕ ţö îḿþŕöVé ŕéļéVåñţ çöḿḿûñîçåţîöñ ƒéåţûŕéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="reset_network_desc_summary">[<li>ŴĻÅÑ</li>"
"<li>Ḿöɓîļé ðåţå</li>"
"<li>βļûéţööţĥ</li> one two three]</string>
    <string name="reset_network_desc_summary_wifi_only">[<li>ŴĻÅÑ</li>"
"<li>βļûéţööţĥ</li> one two]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_title_emui_wifionly">[Ûšé ĜÞŠ åñð ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_title_emui_wifionly">[Ûšé ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_new_details">"[1. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé šîĝñîƒîçåñţļý îḿþŕöVéš ţĥé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ ŕåñĝé åñð îñţéñšîţý öƒ ŴĻÅÑ šîĝñåļš. Öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš çåñ çöññéçţ ţö ýöûŕ çûŕŕéñţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ţĥŕöûĝĥ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé.
2. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé šûþþöŕţš åççéšš ƒŕöḿ ûþ ţö 4 ðéVîçéš.
3. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé ðöéš ñöţ ŵöŕķ ŵîţĥ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ åñð ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ ƒéåţûŕéš. Îƒ ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé îš éñåɓļéð, šöḿé åþþš ţĥåţ ûšé Þ2Þ šéŕVîçéš ḿåý ñöţ ŵöŕķ þŕöþéŕļý.
4. Ûšîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé çöñšûḿéš ɓåţţéŕý þöŵéŕ ḿöŕé Qûîçķļý.
5. Îƒ ýöû ŕéçéîVé å ḿéššåĝé ñöţîƒýîñĝ ýöû ţĥåţ ŴĻÅÑ ŕéšöûŕçéš åŕé ɓéîñĝ ûšéð ɓý åñöţĥéŕ šéŕVîçé, ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš > ŴĻÅÑ > ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ åñð ðîšçöññéçţ åñý çöññéçţéð ðéVîçéš. Öŕ ýöû çåñ ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ öƒƒ åñð ţĥéñ öñ åĝåîñ ţö åûţö-ðîšçöññéçţ åļļ ðéVîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_qrcode_share_notice_new">[Šçåñ ţö çöññéçţ ţö ţĥîš ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_one">"[1. Ḿåķé šûŕé Åççéšš ḿý ļöçåţîöñ îš éñåɓļéð.
2. Šéļéçţ Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ, åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš îñ Ļöçåţîöñ ḿöðé.
3. Çöññéçţ ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ öŕ éñåɓļé ḿöɓîļé ðåţå.
4. Çĥéçķ îƒ ţĥé åþþ ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ ĥåš åççéšš ţö ţĥé Ļöçåţîöñ þéŕḿîššîöñ îñ Þĥöñé ḿåñåĝéŕ > Þéŕḿîššîöñ ḿåñåĝéŕ > Åççéšš ļöçåţîöñ îñƒö.
5. Îƒ ýöû ĥåVé šéţ Ļöçåţîöñ ḿöðé åš Ûšé ĜÞŠ öñļý, þļéåšé ḿåķé šûŕé ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ ļöçåţîöñ åççéšš îñ åñ öþéñ åñð ûñöɓšţŕûçţéð éñVîŕöñḿéñţ ŵĥéŕé ĜÞŠ šîĝñåļš çåñ ɓé ŕéçéîVéð ñöŕḿåļļý.
6. Îƒ ýöû åŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å þûɓļîç ĥöţšþöţ, ţŕý ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ åñð éñåɓļîñĝ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå. Ţĥéñ ţŕý ļöçåţîöñ åççéšš åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_two">"[1. Šéļéçţ Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ, åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš îñ Ļöçåţîöñ ḿöðé ƒöŕ ḿöŕé åççûŕåţé ļöçåţîöñ åççéšš.
2. Îƒ ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ å ḿéţåļ çåšé öñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé, ŕéḿöVé ţĥé çåšé öŕ ûšé å ñöñ-ḿéţåļļîç çåšé åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ.
3. Çĥéçķ îƒ ţĥé åþþ ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ ĥåš åççéšš ţö ţĥé Ļöçåţîöñ þéŕḿîššîöñ îñ Þĥöñé ḿåñåĝéŕ > Þéŕḿîššîöñ ḿåñåĝéŕ > Åççéšš ļöçåţîöñ îñƒö.
4. ÑåVîĝåţîöñ ŵöŕķš ɓéţţéŕ îñ ŵîðé, ûñöɓšţŕûçţéð åŕéåš. Þļåçé ýöûŕ þĥöñé îñ å þöšîţîöñ ñéåŕ ţĥé ŵîñðšĥîéļð öƒ ýöûŕ Véĥîçļé, šûçĥ åš ţĥé ðåšĥɓöåŕð öŕ öţĥéŕ ûñöɓšţŕûçţéð åŕéåš îñ ýöûŕ çåŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_bridge_use_help_new_details_ex">"[»%1$d«. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé šîĝñîƒîçåñţļý îḿþŕöVéš ţĥé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ ŕåñĝé åñð îñţéñšîţý öƒ ŴĻÅÑ šîĝñåļš. Öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš çåñ çöññéçţ ţö ýöûŕ çûŕŕéñţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ţĥŕöûĝĥ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé.
»%2$d«. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé šûþþöŕţš åççéšš ƒŕöḿ ûþ ţö »%6$d« ðéVîçéš.
»%3$d«. ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé ðöéš ñöţ ŵöŕķ ŵîţĥ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ åñð ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ ƒéåţûŕéš. Îƒ ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé îš éñåɓļéð, šöḿé åþþš ţĥåţ ûšé Þ2Þ šéŕVîçéš ḿåý ñöţ ŵöŕķ þŕöþéŕļý.
»%4$d«. Ûšîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ ɓŕîðĝé çöñšûḿéš ɓåţţéŕý þöŵéŕ ḿöŕé Qûîçķļý.
»%5$d«. Îƒ ýöû ŕéçéîVé å ḿéššåĝé ñöţîƒýîñĝ ýöû ţĥåţ ŴĻÅÑ ŕéšöûŕçéš åŕé ɓéîñĝ ûšéð ɓý åñöţĥéŕ šéŕVîçé, ĝö ţö Šéţţîñĝš > ŴĻÅÑ > ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ åñð ðîšçöññéçţ åñý çöññéçţéð ðéVîçéš. Öŕ ýöû çåñ ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ öƒƒ åñð ţĥéñ öñ åĝåîñ ţö åûţö-ðîšçöññéçţ åļļ ðéVîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="wifiap_use_help_details_ex">"[»%1$d«. Ýöû çåñ ûšé å þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ðéVîçé åš ýöûŕ Îñţéŕñéţ åççéšš þöîñţ. Þéŕîþĥéŕåļš çåñ ɓé çöññéçţéð ţö ýöûŕ ðéVîçé ţĥŕöûĝĥ ŴĻÅÑ åñð çöññéçţéð ðéVîçéš ŵîļļ åççéšš ţĥé Îñţéŕñéţ ţĥŕöûĝĥ ţĥé ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķ.
»%2$d«. Ûšîñĝ å þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ŵîļļ ŕéQûîŕé ýöûŕ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå çöññéçţîöñ ţö ɓé éñåɓļéð, åñð ŵîļļ çöñšûḿé šöḿé ðåţå.
»%3$d«. Ûšîñĝ å þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ḿåý ðŕåîñ ýöûŕ ɓåţţéŕý ƒåšţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]"</string>
    <string name="wifiap_connect_help_details_open_ex">"[Ḿåñûåļ çöññéçţîöñ:
»%2$d«. Éñåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ öñ ţåŕĝéţ ðéVîçé, åñð ƒîñð ţĥé ĥöţšþöţ %1$s.
»%3$d«. Çöññéçţ ţö ĥöţšþöţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_one_summary">"[%1$d. Ḿåķé šûŕé Åççéšš ḿý ļöçåţîöñ îš éñåɓļéð.
%2$d. Šéļéçţ Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ, åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš îñ Ļöçåţîöñ ḿöðé.
%3$d. Çöññéçţ ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ öŕ éñåɓļé ḿöɓîļé ðåţå.
%4$d. Çĥéçķ îƒ ţĥé åþþ ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ ĥåš åççéšš ţö ţĥé Ļöçåţîöñ þéŕḿîššîöñ îñ Þĥöñé ḿåñåĝéŕ > Þéŕḿîššîöñ ḿåñåĝéŕ > Åççéšš ļöçåţîöñ îñƒö.
%5$d. Îƒ ýöû ĥåVé šéţ Ļöçåţîöñ ḿöðé åš Ûšé ĜÞŠ öñļý, þļéåšé ḿåķé šûŕé ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ ļöçåţîöñ åççéšš îñ åñ öþéñ åñð ûñöɓšţŕûçţéð éñVîŕöñḿéñţ ŵĥéŕé ĜÞŠ šîĝñåļš çåñ ɓé ŕéçéîVéð ñöŕḿåļļý.
%6$d. Îƒ ýöû åŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å þûɓļîç ĥöţšþöţ, ţŕý ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ åñð éñåɓļîñĝ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå. Ţĥéñ ţŕý ļöçåţîöñ åççéšš åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="location_help_scheme_body_two_summary">"[%1$d. Šéļéçţ Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ, åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš îñ Ļöçåţîöñ ḿöðé ƒöŕ ḿöŕé åççûŕåţé ļöçåţîöñ åççéšš.
%2$d. Îƒ ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ å ḿéţåļ çåšé öñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé, ŕéḿöVé ţĥé çåšé öŕ ûšé å ñöñ-ḿéţåļļîç çåšé åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ.
%3$d. Çĥéçķ îƒ ţĥé åþþ ýöû åŕé ûšîñĝ ĥåš åççéšš ţö ţĥé Ļöçåţîöñ þéŕḿîššîöñ îñ Þĥöñé ḿåñåĝéŕ > Þéŕḿîššîöñ ḿåñåĝéŕ > Åççéšš ļöçåţîöñ îñƒö.
%4$d. ÑåVîĝåţîöñ ŵöŕķš ɓéţţéŕ îñ ŵîðé, ûñöɓšţŕûçţéð åŕéåš. Þļåçé ýöûŕ þĥöñé îñ å þöšîţîöñ ñéåŕ ţĥé ŵîñðšĥîéļð öƒ ýöûŕ Véĥîçļé, šûçĥ åš ţĥé ðåšĥɓöåŕð öŕ öţĥéŕ ûñöɓšţŕûçţéð åŕéåš îñ ýöûŕ çåŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="turn_off_data_saver_message">[Ûšîñĝ å þöŕţåɓļé ĥöţšþöţ ŕéQûîŕéš ðîšåɓļîñĝ Ðåţå šåVéŕ. Ðîšåɓļé¿ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="first_wlan_hotspot_text">[ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ļéţš ýöû šĥåŕé ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕš, ɓûţ ḿåý ðŕåîñ ɓåţţéŕý þöŵéŕ ƒåšţéŕ åñð îñçŕéåšé ðåţå ûšåĝé ƒééš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="hotspot_power_notification_title">[ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ðîšåɓļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="hotspot_power_notification_ticker_text">[ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ ðîšåɓļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="toast_entitle_wifi_need_close">[ŴĻÅÑ îš çöññéçţéð, ƒöŕɓîð ţö öþéñ ţĥîš ƒûñçţîöñ, þļéåšé çļöšé ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_activated_warning_Title">[ŴĻÅÑ ţûŕñéð öñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_turn_off_warning_message_wifiap">"[Ḿöɓîļé ĥöţšþöţ åñð ŴĻÅÑ çåñ'ţ ɓé ţûŕñéð öñ åţ ţĥé šåḿé ţîḿé. Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ¿ one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_turn_off_warning_message_usb">"[ŴĻÅÑ ḿûšţ ɓé ţûŕñéð öƒƒ ñöŵ. Îţ ŵîļļ ɓé åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ţûŕñéð öñ åĝåîñ öñçé ýöûŕ þĥöñé ĥåš çöḿḿûñîçåţéð ŵîţĥ ÅŢ&amp;Ţ'š šéŕVéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="broadcast_ssid_is_show_dialog">[Îƒ ýöû ţûŕñ öƒƒ βŕöåðçåšţ ñéţŵöŕķ ñåḿé (ŠŠÎÐ) öþţîöñ, ýöûŕ þĥöñé ŵîļļ ñöţ ɓé Vîšîɓļé ţö öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš åñð ŵîļļ ñöţ åþþéåŕ îñ ţĥé ļîšţ öƒ åVåîļåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš. Öţĥéŕ ðéVîçéš çåñ šţîļļ çöññéçţ ţö ýöûŕ ĥöţšþöţ ɓý éñţéŕîñĝ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ ñåḿé ḿåñûåļļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one]</string>
    <string name="enable">[Åûţö-çöññéçţîöñ ţö ÅŢ&amp;T Ţ ŴĻÅÑ éñåɓļéð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="disable">[Åûţö-çöññéçţîöñ ţö ÅŢ&amp;T Ţ ŴĻÅÑ ðîšåɓļéð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="auto_connect_wifi_suggestion">[Ŕéšţåŕţ ŴĻÅÑ ƒöŕ ţĥé Åûţö-çöññéçţîöñ šéţţîñĝš ţö ţåķé éƒƒéçţ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_network_detect_summary">[Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ Îñţéŕñéţ åççéššîɓîļîţý ŵĥéñ çöññéçţîñĝ ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="wifi_disable_by_deivice_admin">[ŴĻÅÑ ĥåš ɓééñ ðîšåɓļéð ɓý ţĥé ðéVîçé åðḿîñîšţŕåţöŕ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wifi_required_info_text">[Ţö çöḿþļéţé ţĥé šéţûþ, ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ ñééðš åççéšš ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. Öñçé šéţûþ îš çöḿþļéţé, ýöû çåñ šŵîţçĥ ɓéţŵééñ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå åñð ŴĻÅÑ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setting_frequency_band_title">[ŴĻÅÑ ƒŕéQûéñçý ɓåñð one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_alert_lockdown_by_device_owner">[%1$s ḿåñåĝéš ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð ðöéšñ’ţ åļļöŵ ýöû ţö ḿöðîƒý öŕ ðéļéţé ţĥîš ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. Föŕ ḿöŕé îñƒöŕḿåţîöñ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ åðḿîñîšţŕåţöŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two]</string>
</resources>
