<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="radio_controls_summary">[Ḿåñåĝé ŴĻÅÑ, βļûéţööţĥ, åîŕþļåñé ḿöðé, ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš, &amp; νÞÑš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="wifi_quick_toggle_title">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_quick_toggle_summary">[Ţûŕñ öñ ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings_category">[ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_wizard_title">[Šéļéçţ ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_starting">[Ţûŕñîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ öñ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_stopping">[Ţûŕñîñĝ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_poor_network_detection_summary">"[Ðöñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ ûñļéšš îţ ĥåš ĝööð Îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîVîţý one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_setting_sleep_policy_title">[Ķééþ ŴĻÅÑ öñ ðûŕîñĝ šļééþ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_suspend_optimizations">[ŴĻÅÑ öþţîḿîžåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_suspend_optimizations_summary">[Ḿîñîḿîžé ɓåţţéŕý ûšåĝé ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îš öñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_access_points">[ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_menu_p2p">[ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_wifi_off">[Ţö šéé åVåîļåɓļé ñéţŵöŕķš, ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ öñ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_wifi_on">[Šéåŕçĥîñĝ ƒöŕ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_empty_list_user_restricted">"[Ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåVé þéŕḿîššîöñ ţö çĥåñĝé ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_onstart_pbc">[Þŕéšš ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ Þŕöţéçţéð Šéţûþ ɓûţţöñ öñ ýöûŕ ŕöûţéŕ. Îţ ḿåý ɓé çåļļéð \"ŴÞŠ\" öŕ çöñţåîñ ţĥîš šýḿɓöļ: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="wifi_wps_connected">[Çöññéçţéð ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_scan_always_turnon_message">"[Ţö îḿþŕöVé ļöçåţîöñ åççûŕåçý åñð ƒöŕ öţĥéŕ þûŕþöšéš, %1$s ŵåñţš ţö ţûŕñ öñ ñéţŵöŕķ šçåññîñĝ, éVéñ ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îš öƒƒ.

Åļļöŵ ţĥîš ƒöŕ åļļ åþþš ţĥåţ ŵåñţ ţö šçåñ¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_advanced_titlebar">[ÅðVåñçéð ŴĻÅÑ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_p2p_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ Ðîŕéçţ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_checkbox_text">[Þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_failed_subtext">[Þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ éŕŕöŕ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_ap_text">[Çöñƒîĝûŕé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_tether_configure_subtext">[%1$s %2$s þöŕţåɓļé ŴĻÅÑ ĥöţšþöţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_settings_title">[ŴĻÅÑ Çåļļîñĝ Šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_calling_mode_title">[ŴĻÅÑ Çåļļîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="status_wifi_mac_address">[ŴĻÅÑ ḾÅÇ åððŕéšš one two three]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_high_accuracy_description">[Ûšé ĜÞŠ, ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš ţö éšţîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_battery_saving_description">[Ûšé ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš ţö éšţîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="location_neighborhood_level">[Ļéţ åþþš ûšé ðåţå ƒŕöḿ šöûŕçéš šûçĥ åš ŴĻÅÑ åñð ḿöɓîļé ñéţŵöŕķš ţö ðéţéŕḿîñé ýöûŕ åþþŕöхîḿåţé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="location_neighborhood_level_wifi">[Ļöçåţîöñ ðéţéŕḿîñéð ɓý ŴĻÅÑ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="battery_stats_wifi_running_label">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_on_time">[ŴĻÅÑ öñ ţîḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_on_time">[ŴĻÅÑ öñ ţîḿé one two]</string>
    <string name="power_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="usage_type_wifi_running">[ŴĻÅÑ ŕûññîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="usage_type_data_wifi_send">[ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå šéñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="usage_type_data_wifi_recv">[ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ŕéçéîVéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="battery_action_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="battery_desc_wifi">[βåţţéŕý ûšéð ɓý ŴĻÅÑ one two three]</string>
    <string name="battery_sugg_wifi">"[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ŴĻÅÑ ŵĥéñ ñöţ ûšîñĝ îţ öŕ ŵĥéñ îţ îšñ'ţ åVåîļåɓļé one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="gadget_toggle_wifi">[Ûþðåţîñĝ ŴĻÅÑ šéţţîñĝ one two three]</string>
    <string name="gadget_state_template">[%1$s %2$s one]</string>
    <string name="gadget_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="backup_data_summary">[βåçķ ûþ åþþ ðåţå, ŴĻÅÑ þåššŵöŕðš, åñð öţĥéŕ šéţţîñĝš ţö Ĝööĝļé šéŕVéŕš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="backup_erase_dialog_message">[Šţöþ ɓåçķîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŴĻÅÑ þåššŵöŕðš, ɓööķḿåŕķš, öţĥéŕ šéţţîñĝš, åñð åþþ ðåţå, þļûš éŕåšé åļļ çöþîéš öñ Ĝööĝļé šéŕVéŕš¿ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title">[ŴĻÅÑ šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_editing_network">[Çöññéçţ ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_connecting_network">[Çöññéçţîñĝ ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s… one two three four]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_eap_not_supported">"[Ýöû çåñ'ţ çöñƒîĝûŕé åñ ÉÅÞ ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîöñ ðûŕîñĝ šéţûþ. Åƒţéŕ šéţûþ, ýöû çåñ ðö ţĥåţ îñ Šéţţîñĝš > Ŵîŕéļéšš &amp; ñéţŵöŕķš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twent]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_description_connected">[Ţöûçĥ <b>Ñéхţ</b>" ţö çöñţîñûé ŵîţĥ šéţûþ.

Ţöûçĥ "<b>βåçķ</b> ţö çöññéçţ ţö å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_menu_show_wifi">[Šĥöŵ ŴĻÅÑ ûšåĝé one two three]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_disable_wifi_limit">[Šéţ ŴĻÅÑ ðåţå ļîḿîţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_tab_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ one]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_app_restrict_background_summary">[Ðîšåɓļé ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ðåţå öñ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå ñéţŵöŕķ öñļý. ŴĻÅÑ ŵîļļ ɓé ûšéð îƒ åVåîļåɓļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_app_restrict_dialog">"[Ţĥîš ƒéåţûŕé ḿåý çåûšé åñ åþþ ţĥåţ ðéþéñðš öñ ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ðåţå ţö šţöþ ŵöŕķîñĝ ŵĥéñ ŴĻÅÑ îšñ'ţ åVåîļåɓļé.

Ýöû çåñ ƒîñð ḿöŕé åþþŕöþŕîåţé ðåţå ûšåĝé çöñţŕöļš îñ ţĥé šéţţîñĝš åVåîļåɓļé ŵîţĥîñ ţĥé åþþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="data_usage_restrict_background">"[Îƒ ýöû ŕéšţŕîçţ ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå, šöḿé åþþš åñð šéŕVîçéš ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ûñļéšš ýöû'ŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="data_usage_restrict_background_multiuser">"[Îƒ ýöû ŕéšţŕîçţ ɓåçķĝŕöûñð ḿöɓîļé ðåţå, šöḿé åþþš åñð šéŕVîçéš ŵöñ'ţ ŵöŕķ ûñļéšš ýöû'ŕé çöññéçţéð ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ.

Ţĥîš šéţţîñĝ åƒƒéçţš åļļ ûšéŕš öñ ţĥîš þĥöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_body">[Šéļéçţ ţĥé ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš ţĥåţ åŕé ḿöɓîļé ĥöţšþöţš. Åþþš çåñ ɓé ŕéšţŕîçţéð ƒŕöḿ ûšîñĝ ţĥéšé ñéţŵöŕķš ŵĥéñ ŕûññîñĝ îñ ţĥé ɓåçķĝŕöûñð. Åþþš ḿåý åļšö ĝéñéŕåţé ŵåŕñîñĝš ŵĥéñ ûšîñĝ ţĥéšé ñéţŵöŕķš ƒöŕ ļåŕĝé ðöŵñļöåðš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_wifi">[ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķš one two]</string>
    <string name="data_usage_metered_wifi_disabled">[Ţö šéļéçţ ḿöɓîļé ĥöţšþöţš, ţûŕñ ŴĻÅÑ öñ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="user_add_user_message_long">"[Ýöû çåñ šĥåŕé ţĥîš ðéVîçé ŵîţĥ öţĥéŕ þéöþļé ɓý çŕéåţîñĝ åððîţîöñåļ ûšéŕš. Éåçĥ ûšéŕ ĥåš ţĥéîŕ öŵñ šþåçé, ŵĥîçĥ ţĥéý çåñ çûšţöḿîžé ŵîţĥ ţĥéîŕ öŵñ åþþš, ŵåļļþåþéŕ, åñð šö öñ. Ûšéŕš çåñ åļšö åðĵûšţ ţåɓļéţ šéţţîñĝš ļîķé ŴĻÅÑ ţĥåţ åƒƒéçţ éVéŕýöñé.

Åƒţéŕ ýöû çŕéåţé å ñéŵ ûšéŕ, ţĥåţ þéŕšöñ ñééðš ţö ĝö ţĥŕöûĝĥ å šéţûþ þŕöçéšš.

Åñý ûšéŕ çåñ åççéþţ ûþðåţéð åþþ þéŕḿîššîöñš öñ ɓéĥåļƒ öƒ åļļ öţĥéŕ ûšéŕš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="restriction_wifi_config_title">[ŴĻÅÑ åñð Ḿöɓîļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="restriction_wifi_config_summary">[Åļļöŵ ḿöðîƒîçåţîöñ öƒ ŴĻÅÑ åñð Ḿöɓîļé šéţţîñĝš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setup_title_connected_network_Toast">[Çöññéçţéð ţö ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ %s one two three four]</string>
    <string name="huawei_beam_explained">[Ĥûåŵéî βéåḿ ļéţš ýöû ţŕåñšƒéŕ ƒîļéš, šûçĥ åš þîçţûŕéš, Vîðéöš, çöñţåçţš åñð ÛŔĻš, ɓéţŵééñ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åñð åñöţĥéŕ ÑFÇ-çåþåɓļé ðéVîçé. Ĥûåŵéî βéåḿ îš åçţîVåţéð ɓý þļåçîñĝ ţĥé ţŵö ðéVîçéš çļöšé ţöĝéţĥéŕ (ûšûåļļý ɓåçķ ţö ɓåçķ) åñð ţåþþîñĝ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ. Þļéåšé ñöţé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ βļûéţööţĥ öŕ ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ţûŕñéð öñ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ɓéƒöŕé ƒîļé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="wifi_display_settings_summary">[Ðîšþļåý ýöûŕ þĥöñé šçŕééñ öñ åñöţĥéŕ ðîšþļåý öVéŕ å ŴĻÅÑ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="huawei_beam_front_explained">"[Ĥûåŵéî βéåḿ ļéţš ýöû ţŕåñšƒéŕ ƒîļéš ţö öţĥéŕ ÑFÇ ðéVîçéš ɓý þļåçîñĝ ţĥé ðéVîçéš çļöšé ţöĝéţĥéŕ. Föŕ éхåḿþļé, ýöû çåñ ŵîŕéļéššļý ţŕåñšƒéŕ þîçţûŕéš, Vîðéöš, çöñţåçţš, ÛŔĻš, åñð ḿöŕé ɓéţŵééñ ţŵö ÑFÇ-çåþåɓļé ðéVîçéš. Šîḿþļý:
1. Þļåçé ţĥé ƒŕöñţ þåñéļ öƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åĝåîñšţ åñöţĥéŕ ÑFÇ ðéVîçé, åñð þîçķ ûþ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åƒţéŕ ýöû ĥéåŕ å ţöñé.
2. Ţöûçĥ ýöûŕ šçŕééñ ŵîţĥîñ ţĥŕéé šéçöñðš öƒ ĥéåŕîñĝ ţĥé ţöñé.
3. Þļåçé ţĥé ƒŕöñţ þåñéļ öƒ ýöûŕ ðéVîçé åĝåîñšţ ţĥé öţĥéŕ ÑFÇ ðéVîçé åĝåîñ ţö çöḿþļéţé ţĥé ţŕåñšƒéŕ. Þļéåšé ñöţé ţĥåţ ýöûŕ βļûéţööţĥ öŕ ŴĻÅÑ ḿåý ɓé ţûŕñéð öñ åûţöḿåţîçåļļý ɓéƒöŕé ƒîļé ţŕåñšḿîššîöñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="wifi_required_info_text">[Ţö çöḿþļéţé ţĥé šéţûþ, ýöûŕ ţåɓļéţ ñééðš åççéšš ţö å ŴĻÅÑ ñéţŵöŕķ. Öñçé šéţûþ îš çöḿþļéţé, ýöû çåñ šŵîţçĥ ɓéţŵééñ ḿöɓîļé ðåţå åñð ŴĻÅÑ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fiveteen sixteen seventeen nineteen twenty one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_setting_frequency_band_title">[ŴĻÅÑ ƒŕéQûéñçý ɓåñð one two three]</string>
</resources>
